A Guide to the Fairfax County Office of Public Affairs Photograph Collection, 1962-2009
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 6: Photo and Negative File, 1987-2006
  - Fairfax Film and Video Festival Week (Hanley), 2002 April 29 (Box 23)
  - Health Information Partners Project (Hanley), 2002 April 29 (Box 23)
  - Ake Kids Smile, Inc, (Gross), 2002 April 29 (Box 23)
  - Older Americans Month (Kauffman), 2002 April 29 (Box 23)
  - Safe Kids Week (Hanley), 2002 April 29 (Box 23)
  - Act of Caring Awards (Hyland), 2002 May 6 (Box 23)
  - Hayfield Hawks Boys' Varsity Basketball Team (Kauffman), 2002 May 6 (Box 23)
  - Robinson Secondary School Girls' Cross Country Team (Bulova), 2002 May 6 (Box 23)
  - Foster Care and Foster Family Recognition Month (Hanley), 2002 May 6 (Box 23)
  - Girl Power! Day (Gross), 2002 May 6 (Box 23)
  - Provider Appreciation Day (Hanley), 2002 May 6 (Box 23)
  - Nurses Month (Hanley/Hudgins), 2002 May 6 (Box 23)
  - Public Service Recognition Week (Gross), 2002 May 6 (Box 23)
  - Jennifer Benison (Hyland), 2002 May 20 (Box 23)
  - AmericaCorps National Civilian Community Corps Senate Team 11 (Kauffman), 2002 May 20 (Box 23)
  - Early Intervention Month (Hanley), 2002 May 20 (Box 23)
  - Lynne Pope (Frey), 2002 May 20 (Box 23)
  - Mr. and Mrs. James Mott (McConnell), 2002 May 20 (Box 23)
  - Henley Gabeau (Hyland), 2002 May 20 (Box 23)
  - Betty and Glenn Stroup (Frey), 2002 May 20 (Box 23)
  - National Public Works Week (Hanley), 2002 May 20 (Box 23)
  - Springfield Days (Kauffman/McConnell), 2002 May 20 (Box 23)
  - United States Army 227th Anniversary (Hanley), 2002 June 3 (Box 23)
  - Lord and Lady Fairfax Honorees (Hanley), 2002 June 3 (Box 23)
  - Kilmer Middle School Future City (Mendelsohn/Connolly), 2002 June 3 (Box 23)
  - Christina Ghani (Bulova) & the Lake Braddock Girls' Track Team (Bulova), 2002 June 3 (Box 23)
  - Hepatitis Awareness Day (Hanley), 2002 June 3 (Box 23)
  - Retiring Principals: Vera Blake, Carol Bradley, Beverly Morrison & David Kulp (Connolly/Hudgins/Mendelsohn), 2002 June 17 (Box 23)
  - Emma Henri (Hudgins), 2002 June 17 (Box 23)
  - Stephen McGregor (Hanley), 2002 June 17 (Box 23)
  - Frank de la Fe (Connolly), 2002 June 17 (Box 23)
  - Prostate Cancer Awareness Day (Hanley), 2002 June 17 (Box 23)
  - Responsible Fatherhood Week (Hanley), 2002 June 17 (Box 23)
  - Reston Day (Hudgins), 2002 June 17 (Box 23)
  - Greg Whitaker (Connolly), 2002 July 1 (Box 23)
  - Dennis Nelson (Hudgins), 2002 July 1 (Box 23)
  - Westminnster Builders Club (Gross), 2002 July 1 (Box 23)
  - Sam Clay (Connolly), 2002 July 1 (Box 23)
  - Honor Guard of the Office of the Sheriff (Connolly), 2002 July 22 (Box 23)
  - William Brown (Frey), 2002 July 22 (Box 23)
  - Earth Day/Arbor Day Host, Sponsors & Planning Committee (Bulova), 2002 July 22 (Box 23)
  - Leadership Fairfax Inc. (Frey/Mendelsohn), 2002 July 22 (Box 23)
  - 20th Anniversary of Occoquan Watershed (Hanley), 2002 July 22 (Box 23)
  - Breastfeeding Week (Hanley), 2002 August 5 (Box 23)
  - American Character Week (Hanley), 2002 August 5 (Box 23)
  - Sean Doolan (Hanley), 2002 August 5 (Box 23)
  - Madison High School Softball Team (Hudgins), 2002 August 5 (Box 23)
  - McLean High School Girls' and Boys' Crew Teams (Mendelsohn), 2002 August 5 (Box 23)
  - State Sports Champions from FCPS: Madison High School Baseball Team (Hudgins), 2002 August 5 (Box 23)
  - State Sports Champions from FCPS: Robinson SS Girls' Soccer Team (Hanley), 2002 August 5 (Box 23)
  - State Sports Champions from FCPS: Robinson SS Boys' Lacrosse Team (Hanley), 2002 August 5 (Box 23)
  - State Sports Champions from FCPS: Thomas Jefferson High School Girls' and Boys' Swim and Dive Teams (Hanley), 2002 August 5 (Box 23)
  - State Sports Champions from FCPS: West Springfield High School Boys' Soccer Team (Hanley), 2002 August 5 (Box 23)
  - Lorton Prison Razor Wire Cutting Ceremony, 2002 August 24 (Box 24)
  - Harmony Heritage Singers (Hanley), 2002 September 9 (Box 24)
  - A Day of Remembrance: An Interfaith Gathering United for Peace (Hanley), 2002 September 9 (Box 24)
  - Remembrance Week (Connolly), 2002 September 9 (Box 24)
  - Civic Participation Week (Connolly), 2002 September 9 (Box 24)
  - Bull Run Elementary School Odyssey of the Mind Teams (Frey), 2002 September 9 (Box 24)
  - Substance Abuse Awareness Week (Hanley), 2002 September 9 (Box 24)
  - Older Adult Expo Planning Committee (Gross), 2002 September 9 (Box 24)
  - Hispanic Heritage Month (Hanley), 2002 September 9 (Box 24)
  - Food Safety Education Month (Hanley), 2002 September 9 (Box 24)
  - September 11th Memorial Grove Ceremony, 2002 September 9 (Box 24)
  - Peter Brinitzer (Hyland), 2002 September 23 (Box 24)
  - Disability Employment Awareness (Hanley), 2002 September 23 (Box 24)
  - "Ride to Remember" (Connolly and Gross), 2002 September 23 (Box 24)
  - Annandale Christian Community for Action (Gross), 2002 September 23 (Box 24)
  - Kingstowne Faith 5K Run/Walk (Kauffman), 2002 September 23 (Box 24)
  - Ovarian Cancer Awareness Week (Hudgins), 2002 September 23 (Box 24)
  - Anna Marlow (Mendelsohn), 2002 September 23 (Box 24)
  - Daniel Bickham (Gross), 2002 September 23 (Box 24)
  - Long Term Care Awareness Week (Hanley), 2002 September 23 (Box 24)
  - Northern Virginia Technology Council Foundation (Hyland), 2002 September 23 (Box 24)
  - Fire Prevention Week (Hanley), 2002 September 23 (Box 24)
  - Department of Transportation (Connolly), 2002 September 23 (Box 24)
  - Clermont Elementary (Kauffman), 2002 September 23 (Box 24)
  - Novgorod Alliance (Bulova), 2002 October 7 (Box 24)
  - Mental Illness Awareness Week (Hanley), 2002 October 7 (Box 24)
  - Katherine Clark (Hudgins), 2002 October 7 (Box 24)
  - Paul Baldino (Hyland), 2002 October 7 (Box 24)
  - Park Authority (Mendelsohn), 2002 October 7 (Box 24)
  - VolunteerFest® (Hanley), 2002 October 7 (Box 24)
  - Franconia Volunteer Fire Department (Kauffman), 2002 October 7 (Box 24)
  - Armand Malo (Hyland), 2002 October 28 (Box 24)
  - Shirley Long (Mendelsohn), 2002 October 28 (Box 24)
  - Gerald Halpin (Hyland), 2002 October 28 (Box 24)
  - Rony Avalos and the Vienna Firefighters (Hyland), 2002 October 28 (Box 24)
  - Ben Ettleman and Davis Industries (Hyland), 2002 October 28 (Box 24)
  - Gold's Gym (Hudgins), 2002 October 28 (Box 24)
  - Adoption Awareness Month (Hanley), 2002 October 28 (Box 24)
  - Volunteer Home Repair Program (Gross), 2002 October 28 (Box 24)
  - Fairfax County Recycles Day (Hanley), 2002 October 28 (Box 24)
  - American Indian Heritage Month (Hanley), 2002 October 28 (Box 24)
  - Park Authority (Kauffman), 2002 October 28 (Box 24)
  - Route 123 Widening Project (Connolly), 2002 November 18 (Box 24)
  - World AIDS Day, Loretta Beckman & Dr. David Wheeler (Hanley), 2002 November 18 (Box 24)
  - Stevenson Street Project (Bulova & McConnell), 2002 November 18 (Box 24)
  - 100th Anniversary of First Korean Immigrants (McConnell), 2002 November 18 (Box 24)
  - Lynn Hiltajczuk (Kauffman), 2002 November 18 (Box 24)
  - Student Officers of Election and Election Pages, 2002 December 9 (Box 24)
  - Diane Miller, 2002 December 9 (Box 24)
  - Community Challenges Task Force, 2002 December 9 (Box 24)
  - Truro Community, 2002 December 9 (Box 24)
  - Judith Isom, 2002 December 9 (Box 24)
  - Judith Silverstein, 2002 December 9 (Box 24)
  - Firefighter Combat Challenge Team and Soza & Company, Ltd., 2003 January 6 (Box 25)
  - COX Communications and Fairfax County Police Department, 2003 January 6 (Box 25)
  - Audrey Slyman, 2003 January 6 (Box 25)
  - Monica Perz-Waddington, 2003 January 6 (Box 25)
  - 2002 Fall Bond Referendum Committee, 2003 January 6 (Box 25)
  - National Mentoring Month, 2003 January 6 (Box 25)
  - Robert Athing, 2003 January 6 (Box 25)
  - Department of Human Resources, 2003 January 6 (Box 25)
  - Southwestern Youth Association, 2003 January 27 (Box 25)
  - African-American History Month, 2003 January 27 (Box 25)
  - John Robinson, 2003 January 27 (Box 25)
  - Forest Edge Elementary School and Siemens ICN, Inc., 2003 February 10 (Box 25)
  - Friends of the Reston Regional Library, 2003 February 10 (Box 25)
  - National Engineers Week, 2003 February 10 (Box 25)
  - Oakton High School Football, 2003 February 24 (Box 25)
  - Women’s History Month, 2003 February 24 (Box 25)
  - National Purchasing Month, 2003 February 24 (Box 25)
  - Developmental Disabilities Inclusion, 2003 February 24 (Box 25)
  - Al Hillman, 2003 March 10 (Box 25)
  - Celebrate Fairfax!, 2003 March 10 (Box 25)
  - Alternative Dispute Resolution, 2003 March 10 (Box 25)
  - Northern Virginia Mediation Service, 2003 March 10 (Box 25)
  - Red Cross Month, 2003 March 10 (Box 25)
  - 30th Anniversary of the Commission on Aging, 2003 March 10 (Box 25)
  - Sandra Chisholm, 2003 March 10 (Box 25)
  - Lu Ellingwood, 2003 March 24 (Box 25)
  - Steve Titunik, Jennifer Feinstein and State Trooper Michael Walter, 2003 March 24 (Box 25)
  - Child Abuse Prevention Month, 2003 March 24 (Box 25)
  - Lego League Teams of Hunter Woods Elementary, 2003 March 24 (Box 25)
  - Tuberculosis Awareness Day, 2003 March 24 (Box 25)
  - Public Health Week, 2003 March 24 (Box 25)
  - South Lakes High School Theatre Department, 2003 April 7 (Box 25)
  - Bike to Work Day, 2003 April 7 (Box 25)
  - Donate Life Month, 2003 April 7 (Box 25)
  - Medical Care for Children Partnership, Computer Learning, Adopt-A-Family and Project Discovery, 2003 April 7 (Box 25)
  - Building Safety Week, 2003 April 7 (Box 25)
  - Fair Housing Month, 2003 April 7 (Box 25)
  - Mission of Mercy Dental Project, 2003 April 7 (Box 25)
  - Volunteer Recognition Day, 2003 April 7 (Box 25)
  - Fairfax Education Association Retirement Housing Corporation of Virginia, 2003 April 7 (Box 25)
  - Immunization Month, 2003 April 7 (Box 25)
  - Alicia Harder, 2003 April 28 (Box 25)
  - Christine Lamb, 2003 April 28 (Box 25)
  - “Bears in Cruisers”, 2003 April 28 (Box 25)
  - Foster Care and Foster Family Recognition Month, 2003 April 28 (Box 25)
  - Asian/Pacific American Heritage Month, 2003 April 28 (Box 25)
  - Health Nurses Day, 2003 April 28 (Box 25)
  - Safe Kids Week, 2003 April 28 (Box 25)
  - Edward Stinnette, 2003 April 28 (Box 25)
  - Older Americans Month, 2003 April 28 (Box 25)
  - William Brannon, 2003 May 5 (Box 25)
  - Kath Vernon, 2003 May 5 (Box 25)
  - Harold Henderson, 2003 May 5 (Box 25)
  - Jane Gwinn, 2003 May 5 (Box 25)
  - Community Action Month, 2003 May 5 (Box 25)
  - Suicide Prevention Week, 2003 May 5 (Box 25)
  - 50th Anniversary of Great Falls Elementary School, 2003 May 5 (Box 25)
  - Mental Health Awareness Month, 2003 May 5 (Box 25)
  - Stroke Awareness Day, 2003 May 5 (Box 25)
  - Springfield Days, 2003 May 5 (Box 25)
  - South Lakes High School, 2003 May 5 (Box 25)
  - South Lakes Basketball and Football Teams, 2003 May 5 (Box 25)
  - Public Service Recognition Week, 2003 May 5 (Box 25)
  - Marshall High School Theater Department, 2003 May 19 (Box 25)
  - Tower Center Merchants Association, 2003 May 19 (Box 25)
  - 150th Anniversary of Oliver Episcopal Church, 2003 May 19 (Box 25)
  - 288th Anniversary of the United States Army, 2003 June 2 (Box 25)
  - 2003 Lord and Lady Fairfax Honorees, 2003 June 2 (Box 25)
  - Girl Power!, 2003 June 2 (Box 25)
  - Christina Aponte and Kelly Morgan, 2003 June 2 (Box 25)
  - Save a Life Season, 2003 June 2 (Box 25)
  - Reston Watershed Action Group, 2003 June 2 (Box 25)
  - Clean Water Partnership, 2003 June 2 (Box 25)
  - Sponsors and Planning Committee of Earth Day/Arbor Day, 2003 June 16 (Box 25)
  - Hepatitis Awareness DAY, 2003 June 16 (Box 25)
  - Retiring Fairfax County School Principals, 2003 June 16 (Box 25)
  - Lina Jee Hyan Kang, 2003 June 16 (Box 25)
  - Fairhill Elementary School Mean, Lean, Green Awesomely Supreme Recycling, 2003 June 16 (Box 25)
  - Responsible Fatherhood Week, 2003 June 16 (Box 25)
  - Freddie Mac Foundation, 2003 July 7 (Box 26)
  - Parks and Recreation Month, 2003 July 7 (Box 26)
  - Robert Boxer, 2003 July 7 (Box 26)
  - Inge Pisano, 2003 July 7 (Box 26)
  - James Madison High School Baseball and Softball Teams, 2003 July 21 (Box 26)
  - Community Dialogue on Transportation and Land Use, 2003 July 21 (Box 26)
  - Lydia Thomas, 2003 July 21 (Box 26)
  - Lorton Computer Learning Centers Partnership, 2003 July 21 (Box 26)
  - Herndon Free Clinic, 2003 July 21 (Box 26)
  - Garfield Elementary School, 2003 August 4 (Box 26)
  - Roberts Breads, 2003 August 4 (Box 26)
  - Michael Butters, 2003 September 15 (Box 26)
  - Vienna Volunteer Fire Department, 2003 September 15 (Box 26)
  - Hispanic Heritage Month, 2003 September 15 (Box 26)
  - Combined Charitable Campaign Month, 2003 September 15 (Box 26)
  - Substance Abuse Awareness Month, 2003 September 15 (Box 26)
  - FCPS Top High Schools in America for 2003, 2003 September 29 (Box 26)
  - McLean Little League 9-10 and 11-12 Softball All-Stars and McLean Babe Ruth Boys’ U-14 All-Stars, 2003 September 29 (Box 26)
  - James Edmondson, William Ehlman and Robert Greenburg, 2003 September 29 (Box 26)
  - Disability Employment Awareness Month, 2003 September 29 (Box 26)
  - Mental Illness Awareness Week, 2003 September 29 (Box 26)
  - Fire Prevention Week, 2003 September 29 (Box 26)
  - Voter Education Month, 2003 September 29 (Box 26)
  - Adele Lebowitz, 2003 October 20 (Box 26)
  - West Springfield Little League 9-10 and 11-12 All-Star Teams, 2003 October 20 (Box 26)
  - VolunteerFest Day, 2003 October 20 (Box 26)
  - Citizens and developers who have made properties for training available for Fairfax County Public Safety, 2003 October 20 (Box 26)
  - Judith Mueller, 2003 October 20 (Box 26)
  - Trudy Brisendene, 2003 October 20 (Box 26)
  - America Recycles Day, 2003 October 20 (Box 26)
  - Forest Edge Elementary School Odyssey of the Mind Odd Pod Structure Team, 2003 October 27 (Box 26)
  - Fairfax Stars Girls’ 13 -and- under and 15-and-under Basketball Teams, 2003 October 27 (Box 26)
  - Native American Heritage Month, 2003 October 27 (Box 26)
  - Retiring Fairfax County Public Schools Members, 2003 November 17 (Box 26)
  - Private and Public sectors who assisted during Hurricane Isabel, 2003 November 17 (Box 26)
  - Adoption Awareness Month, 2003 November 17 (Box 26)
  - Sharon Kelso, 2003 November 17 (Box 26)
  - Main Street Child Development Center, 2003 November 17 (Box 26)
  - Worlds AIDS Day, 2003 November 17 (Box 26)
  - Auxiliary Police Officers Program, 2003 November 17 (Box 26)
  - Carol Stuart-Goldberg, 2003 November 17 (Box 26)
  - James Allred, 2003 December 8 (Box 26)
  - Herndon High School Girls’ Cross-Country Team, 2003 December 8 (Box 26)
  - Student Election Officers and Student Election Pages, 2003 December 8 (Box 26)
  - Dewey Bond, 2003 December 8 (Box 26)
  - Greater Reston Chamber of Commerce Incubator Program, 2003 December 8 (Box 26)
  - Morning Star Program, 2003 December 8 (Box 26)
  - 30th Anniversary of United Christian Parish and Suzanne Rudisell for 15 years as pastor, 2003 December 8 (Box 26)
  - 20th anniversary of Reston Triathlon, 2003 December 8 (Box 26)
  - Medical Care for Children Partnership, 2003 December 8 (Box 26)
  - National Mentoring Month, 2003 December 8 (Box 26)
  - Spring Hill RECenter Shotokan Karate Team, 2003 December 8 (Box 26)
  - 30th Anniversary of Fairfax County Urban Forestry Program, 2003 December 8 (Box 26)
  - Officers Alfreda and Becker, Dispatcher Ortiz, 2004 January 5 (Box 27)
  - Kingstowne Faith 5K Run/Walk, 2004 January 5 (Box 27)
  - James Warfield, 2004 January 5 (Box 27)
  - Master Technician John Mayers - 2003 Career Firefighter of the Year, 2004 January 5 (Box 27)
  - Sam Pixley, 2004 January 5 (Box 27)
  - Chief J. Thomas Manger, 2004 January 26 (Box 27)
  - Jane Kornblut, 2004 January 26 (Box 27)
  - African American History Month, 2004 January 26 (Box 27)
  - Give Kids a Smile! National Children’s Dental Access Day, 2004 January 26 (Box 27)
  - Richard Combs, 2004 January 26 (Box 27)
  - Jerry Hubbard, 2004 January 26 (Box 27)
  - Diane Mclntyre, 2004 January 26 (Box 27)
  - James Madison High School Football Team, 2004 February 9 (Box 27)
  - Youth Leadership Program, 2004 February 9 (Box 27)
  - Associated Builders and Contractors, 2004 February 9 (Box 27)
  - 29th Infantry Division of the National Guard, 2004 February 9 (Box 27)
  - Barbara Gernat, 2004 February 9 (Box 27)
  - Lyn Ganschinietz, 2004 February 9 (Box 27)
  - Westfield High School Football Team, 2004 February 23 (Box 27)
  - Virginia Run Turkey Trot, 2004 February 23 (Box 27)
  - Jack Kelso, 2004 February 23 (Box 27)
  - Purchasing Month, 2004 February 23 (Box 27)
  - A Bias Incident, 2004 February 23 (Box 27)
  - National Engineers Week, 2004 February 23 (Box 27)
  - Richard Combs, 2004 March 8 (Box 27)
  - Including People with Developmental Disabilities Month, 2004 March 8 (Box 27)
  - Winston Bray, Richard F. Mortimer, and Frederick W. Suffa, 2004 March 8 (Box 27)
  - Red Cross Month, 2004 March 8 (Box 27)
  - Redevelopment and Housing Authority, Housing and Community Development, 2004 March 8 (Box 27)
  - Women’s History Month, 2004 March 8 (Box 27)
  - Honorable Mark Sickles, 2004 March 15 (Box 27)
  - Alicia Harder and Alexis Kuiper, 2004 March 15 (Box 27)
  - John Shughrue Jr., 2004 March 15 (Box 27)
  - Sharon Kelso, 2004 March 15 (Box 27)
  - Tuberculosis Awareness Day, 2004 March 15 (Box 27)
  - 50th Anniversary of the Thomas Jefferson Library, 2004 March 15 (Box 27)
  - Alternative Dispute Resolution, 2004 March 15 (Box 27)
  - Elizabeth High, 2004 March 15 (Box 27)
  - Langley High School Gymnastics, 2004 March 29 (Box 27)
  - Child Abuse Prevention Month, 2004 March 29 (Box 27)
  - Building Safety Week, 2004 March 29 (Box 27)
  - Volunteer Recognition Day, 2004 March 29 (Box 27)
  - Public Health Week, 2004 March 29 (Box 27)
  - Immunization Month, 2004 March 29 (Box 27)
  - Fair Housing Month, 2004 March 29 (Box 27)
  - Donate Life Month, 2004 March 29 (Box 27)
  - South Lakes High School Girls’ Freestyle Relay Team, 2004 April 26 (Box 27)
  - Westfields High School Track and Field Teams, 2004 April 26 (Box 27)
  - Bike to Work day, 2004 April 26 (Box 27)
  - Foster Care and Foster Family Recognition Month, 2004 April 26 (Box 27)
  - Asian/Pacific American Heritage Month, 2004 April 26 (Box 27)
  - Vietnamese Remembrance Month, 2004 April 26 (Box 27)
  - Community Action Month, 2004 April 26 (Box 27)
  - Nurses Month, 2004 April 26 (Box 27)
  - Older Americans Month, 2004 April 26 (Box 27)
  - Soil and Water Stewardship Week, 2004 April 26 (Box 27)
  - Alexis Kuiper, 2004 May 10 (Box 27)
  - Reston Community Center, 2004 May 10 (Box 27)
  - Early Intervention Awareness Month, 2004 May 10 (Box 27)
  - 10th Anniversary of the Fairfax County Public Library Foundation, 2004 May 10 (Box 27)
  - Public Works Week, 2004 May 10 (Box 27)
  - Rose Lambert, 2004 May 10 (Box 27)
  - Ashley Ritz, 2004 May 24 (Box 27)
  - Girl Power Day, 2004 May 24 (Box 27)
  - Alta Newman, 2004 May 24 (Box 27)
  - Springfield Days, 2004 May 24 (Box 27)
  - James Lee Community Day, 2004 May 24 (Box 27)
  - U.S Army Week, 2004 June 7 (Box 27)
  - Lord and Lady Fairfax Honorees, 2004 June 7 (Box 27)
  - Virginia MathCounts Team, 2004 June 7 (Box 27)
  - Earth Day/Arbor Day 2004, 2004 June 7 (Box 27)
  - Fairfax County’s Community Recycling Road Show, 2004 June 7 (Box 27)
  - Direct Care Workers Week, 2004 June 7 (Box 27)
  - Honorable Mark Sickles, 2004 June 21 (Box 27)
  - Bull Run Elementary School Chess Team, 2004 June 21 (Box 27)
  - Patricia Zissios, 2004 June 21 (Box 27)
  - Responsible Fatherhood Week, 2004 June 21 (Box 27)
  - Hepatitis Awareness Day, 2004 June 21 (Box 27)
  - Rick Harvey, 2004 July 12 (Box 28)
  - Nova United Senior Women’s Basketball Teams and Northern Virginia Hawks Senior Men’s Basketball Team, 2004 July 12 (Box 28)
  - Jean White, 2004 July 12 (Box 28)
  - Liz and Bill Faria, 2004 July 12 (Box 28)
  - Barry Brady, 2004 July 12 (Box 28)
  - Christopher Companies, Habitat for Humanity, the Briarwood Citizens’ Association, and Fairfax County Department of Housing and Community Development, 2004 July 12 (Box 28)
  - 20th Anniversary of the Annandale Central Business District Planning Committee, 2004 July 12 (Box 28)
  - Middle East Partnership Initiative, 2004 July 20 (Box 28)
  - Tom Farley, 2004 July 26 (Box 28)
  - Clyde’s Restaurant Group, 2004 July 26 (Box 28)
  - Jack D. Dale, 2004 August 2 (Box 28)
  - Alice Starr, 2004 August 2 (Box 28)
  - West Potomac High School Step Team, 2004 August 2 (Box 28)
  - Department of Fire & Rescue, 2004 August 2 (Box 28)
  - Donald Burns, 2004 August 2 (Box 28)
  - Brittany Niemiec, 2004 August 2 (Box 28)
  - Fairfax County Public Library, 2004 August 2 (Box 28)
  - IT/Web Content Cream of the Crop, 2004 August 2 (Box 28)
  - Da Hieu Youth Alliance Visit to the Fairfax County Government Center, 2004 August 5 (Box 28)
  - Busan City Council Visit to the Fairfax County Government Center, 2004 August 17 (Box 28)
  - Property made available to Public Safety for training by citizens and developers, 2004 September 13 (Box 28)
  - Fairfax Prepares Month, 2004 September 13 (Box 28)
  - Divya Nettimi, 2004 September 13 (Box 28)
  - Dee Cotton, Eileen Mead and Gertrude Porch, 2004 September 13 (Box 28)
  - Jewish Heritage Month, 2004 September 13 (Box 28)
  - American Youth Philharmonic Orchestras - 40th anniversary, 2004 September 13 (Box 28)
  - Hispanic Heritage Month, 2004 September 13 (Box 28)
  - Nigerian Delegation Visit to Fairfax County Government, 2004 September 22 (Box 28)
  - Carter Gospel Singers, 2004 September 27 (Box 28)
  - McLean Little League 11-12-Year-Old Girls’ All-Star Softball Team, 2004 September 27 (Box 28)
  - Mental Illness Awareness Month, 2004 September 27 (Box 28)
  - Marth Glennan, 2004 September 27 (Box 28)
  - Carol Coryell, 2004 September 27 (Box 28)
  - Fire Prevention Week, 2004 September 27 (Box 28)
  - Braddock District Community Dialog, 2004 September 27 (Box 28)
  - Oakton Classic Day, 2004 September 27 (Box 28)
  - Domestic Violence Awareness Month, 2004 September 27 (Box 28)
  - Food Safety Education Month, 2004 September 27 (Box 28)
  - Cable Channel 16, 2004 September 27 (Box 28)
  - Adoption Awareness Month, 2004 October 18 (Box 28)
  - Disability Employment Awareness Month, 2004 October 18 (Box 28)
  - American Indian Heritage Month, 2004 October 18 (Box 28)
  - Luther Jackson Middle School Week, 2004 October 18 (Box 28)
  - Rose Hill Community’s 50th Anniversary, 2004 October 18 (Box 28)
  - Fred Morin, 2004 October 18 (Box 28)
  - Kenneth Klinge, 2004 October 18 (Box 28)
  - Richard Risk, 2004 October 18 (Box 28)
  - VolunteerFest Day, 2004 October 18 (Box 28)
  - Breast Cancer Awareness Month, 2004 October 18 (Box 28)
  - CHARACTER COUNTS Week, 2004 October 18 (Box 28)
  - After school Day!, 2004 October 18 (Box 28)
  - County Executive & staff & County’s Budget for exemplary work, 2004 October 18 (Box 28)
  - Town of Vienna for Hosting Capital Holiday Tree Festival, 2004 November 15 (Box 28)
  - McLean Little League 9-10 Softball All-Stars, 2004 November 15 (Box 28)
  - Chantilly pyramid Minority Student Achievement Committee, 2004 November 15 (Box 28)
  - Substance Abuse Awareness Week, 2004 November 15 (Box 28)
  - Springfield United Methodist Church, 2004 November 15 (Box 28)
  - Deborah Tyler, 2004 November 15 (Box 28)
  - Pamela Danner, 2004 November 15 (Box 28)
  - Jack Wilbern, 2004 November 15 (Box 28)
  - Andy Szakos, 2004 November 15 (Box 28)
  - James Gorby, 2004 November 15 (Box 28)
  - American Recycles Day, 2004 November 15 (Box 28)
  - AIDS Awareness Day, 2004 November 15 (Box 28)
  - Jeanette Stewart, 2004 December 6 (Box 28)
  - Fairfax County Fire Department, 2004 December 6 (Box 28)
  - County Staff for Hurricane Charley, 2004 December 6 (Box 28)
  - Kim Ifeora & Sung Pyun, 2004 December 6 (Box 28)